It’s just the beginning.
Halftime is a documentary, music film directed by Amanda Micheli.
Global superstar Jennifer Lopez reflects on her multifaceted career and the
pressure of life in the spotlight in this intimate documentary.
Self, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Self, played by Ben Affleck.
Self, played by Lorene Scafaria.
Self, played by Shakira.
Self, played by Laura Dern.
Self, played by Constance Wu.
Jennifer Lopez: Halftime is a 2022 American Netflix original
documentary film directed by Amanda Micheli.
Its story follows the career of Jennifer Lopez, with a heavy focus on her
performance at the Super Bowl LIV halftime show and her film Hustlers (2019).
The film premiered at the opening night of the 2022 Tribeca Film
Festival, and was released on Netflix on June 14, 2022.
Lopez re-recorded an orchestra version of the song entitled "Same Girl (Halftime Remix)" featuring French Montana along with another
song, a rendition of "This Land Is Your Land" / "America the Beautiful", to coincide with the release of the film.
The film explores themes of pop culture, pop singer, woman director.